Christopher Gomez

661-281-4853 c.gomez3644@gmail.com

SUMMARY

I am an experienced software engineer working in the video game industry with multiple shipped titles, interactive software, and a background in technology and art. I have a strong work ethic, a desire to exceed expectations, and the ability to adapt to new situations and learn quickly. I am interested in pushing the boundaries between software and human-computer interaction, utilizing the latest cutting edge technologies to create memorable experiences and useful applications.

EXPERIENCE

WayForward Technologies, Full Stack Engineer

Backend Systems, Frontend Frameworks, and Unity Engine Valencia, CA --- 2019 - Current

College of the Canyons, Lead Computer Science Tutor / Technical Support

Computer Science tutor, Canvas support, and computer troubleshooter

Valencia, CA --- 2017 - 2019

Gamestop Senior Sales Associate

Customer service and retail position and a local video game store.

Valencia. CA --- 2015 - 2017

EDUCATION

California State University, Northridge

Aug 2017 - May 2019 Bachelors of Science - Computer Science

College of the Canyons

Aug 2015 - Jun 2017 Associates of Science - Computer Science Associates of Science - Mathematics

Seattle University

Aug 2013 - Jun 2015

SKILLS

- JavaScript/NodeJS/React, C#, Python, C++, CI/CD, Databases, Game Engines.
- Real Time Networking (Sockets/STT/HLS).
- Systems, Algorithms, Data, Analytics, Retention Strategies, and Monetization.
- Exceptional listener and communicator who effectively conveys information verbally and in writing.
- Highly analytical thinking with demonstrated talent for identifying, scrutinizing, improving, and streamlining complex work processes.
- Innovative problem-solver who can generate workable solutions and resolve issues quickly and efficiently.

Accomplishments

- Successfully ported s PC game to every console and TV streaming box.
- Won a daytime Emmy for Outstanding Interactive Media.
- Worked closely with Nintendo of America to release a successful 2nd party title.
- Decreased development time by optimizing the CI/CD pipelines for many applications and games at my company using TeamCity and Azure.